{
  "queues": [
    {
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": "8b5c5e86-f65b-4172-aa5b-1aed055118be",
          "front": "1 × 3 = ?",
          "back": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "70bcb183-b5cd-4e45-b253-daef858a0783",
          "front": "1 × 4 = ?",
          "back": "4"
        },
        {
          "id": "63da07a2-d58a-45eb-910c-0eca97b288c1",
          "front": "1 × 5 = ?",
          "back": "5"
        },
        {
          "id": "686c3bf3-7701-4408-b34f-d9494625d18b",
          "front": "1 × 6 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        },
        {
          "id": "4a5463c3-a37c-4772-9eda-4d08e72a9248",
          "front": "1 × 7 = ?",
          "back": "7"
        },
        {
          "id": "00488095-9f5e-4b14-9e33-5cd1b01a5fac",
          "front": "1 × 8 = ?",
          "back": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "4721f9e2-7574-4143-a3ff-568ca52d973c",
          "front": "1 × 9 = ?",
          "back": "9"
        },
        {
          "id": "eb158acd-5628-4fdb-8565-34eec7719846",
          "front": "2 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "2"
        },
        {
          "id": "910b08ec-2bea-44f5-9ce9-c917bcf8a08b",
          "front": "2 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "4"
        },
        {
          "id": "894b2cff-beab-4856-a755-09939ceca0eb",
          "front": "2 × 3 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        },
        {
          "id": "a71f98a3-ec96-43ea-b08e-07e67f1abc07",
          "front": "2 × 4 = ?",
          "back": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "a4721203-dab7-4436-949f-78c0d2f74fd4",
          "front": "2 × 5 = ?",
          "back": "10"
        },
        {
          "id": "6b2de9aa-afc0-49a1-b89c-c6a0184d4ff8",
          "front": "2 × 6 = ?",
          "back": "12"
        },
        {
          "id": "67744823-b669-4f34-9db0-b18e418a0e27",
          "front": "2 × 7 = ?",
          "back": "14"
        },
        {
          "id": "fc6f8c63-7a88-4304-b3b5-d8a0601ab3c8",
          "front": "2 × 8 = ?",
          "back": "16"
        },
        {
          "id": "19d1808e-0d59-4139-8684-c5b935c421ef",
          "front": "2 × 9 = ?",
          "back": "18"
        },
        {
          "id": "45511cda-e112-4a46-8ce7-d77188877eb2",
          "front": "3 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "9626bb2e-48fc-4ce2-89e5-183170894008",
          "front": "3 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        }
      ],
      "capacity": 20
    },
    {
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": "003fcd37-dc94-459e-b3e4-4b438ad8e300",
          "front": "1 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "2"
        },
        {
          "id": "22f6846c-0c22-4f2c-866c-69f06388f317",
          "front": "1 × 3 = ?",
          "back": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "d4a37055-ce86-4fbc-bd25-b18204db745d",
          "front": "1 × 4 = ?",
          "back": "4"
        },
        {
          "id": "e49b9bd1-7068-41ba-9b3b-21ec341190ff",
          "front": "1 × 5 = ?",
          "back": "5"
        },
        {
          "id": "7e65abba-4e51-4042-be7f-5d8dfde446dc",
          "front": "1 × 6 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        },
        {
          "id": "9c9ec2f2-f24b-485d-be4a-682cf5249614",
          "front": "1 × 7 = ?",
          "back": "7"
        },
        {
          "id": "5f8f0188-a7ac-4905-9283-87b45caf66d0",
          "front": "1 × 8 = ?",
          "back": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "8b9e676e-98c2-46f2-941d-433fbfa77812",
          "front": "1 × 9 = ?",
          "back": "9"
        },
        {
          "id": "a36d0096-3de2-4064-9e72-45ff9dcc78bf",
          "front": "2 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "2"
        },
        {
          "id": "d3a887da-ade1-4a25-a970-a25208676579",
          "front": "2 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "4"
        },
        {
          "id": "717d4a6c-acd1-4467-845a-d1511c6c2786",
          "front": "2 × 3 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        },
        {
          "id": "674db82b-84a1-41e1-bb74-03361a5a11d7",
          "front": "2 × 4 = ?",
          "back": "8"
        },
        {
          "id": "f19ad655-805f-4c21-b979-77e115ce8520",
          "front": "2 × 5 = ?",
          "back": "10"
        },
        {
          "id": "393e2cc2-051a-4152-9a32-2b92dc724be0",
          "front": "2 × 6 = ?",
          "back": "12"
        },
        {
          "id": "63f3ff36-048f-4f4f-afa7-460958eb1cee",
          "front": "2 × 7 = ?",
          "back": "14"
        },
        {
          "id": "3520ad3e-07d9-4c2c-9c97-8dac2c16748c",
          "front": "2 × 8 = ?",
          "back": "16"
        },
        {
          "id": "dde4df8a-62b5-4abe-970f-0a834611cd4a",
          "front": "2 × 9 = ?",
          "back": "18"
        },
        {
          "id": "fbf65e3b-7bd9-4d8f-917d-6f78a3611b8f",
          "front": "3 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "3"
        },
        {
          "id": "68b00d17-99cd-4882-b250-f7cda582e867",
          "front": "3 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "6"
        },
        {
          "id": "d6cbd14f-9a84-4e4b-b305-06ce7305fee7",
          "front": "1 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "618c4673-6310-4ad2-9a1d-4bd6d9a939c2",
          "front": "1 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": "7b55554f-ab43-4a19-961f-437b14c70a59",
          "front": "1 × 2 = ?",
          "back": "2"
        }
      ],
      "capacity": 40
    },
    {
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": "4ac01258-39b8-4806-a024-b442c68159f0",
          "front": "1 × 1 = ?",
          "back": "1"
        }
      ],
      "capacity": 100
    },
    {
      "cards": [],
      "capacity": 160
    },
    {
      "cards": [],
      "capacity": 280
    }
  ]
}